Finding Aid for the Delmore Schwartz Papers LSC.1005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books from the library of Delmore Schwartz
  - Zebra-striped hearse. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: PS3525.I486 1964 (Box 50)
  - Three roads. New York: Bantam Books, 1960, Call number: PS3525.I486 T46 1960 (Box 53)
  - Chill. Toronto; New York: Bantam Books, 1965, Call number: PS3525.I486 C5 1965 (Box 56)
  - I, spy. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1963, Call number: PR9199.3.M325 D68 1963 (Box 57)
  - Ecliptic. London: Faber & Faber limited, 1930, Call number: PR6025.M2139e; Wrappers stapled to pressboard folder. DS's signature dated December 1933. (Box 70)
    Gift of J. Howard Woolmer, 1988.
  - Poetry of W. B. Yeats. London, New York [etc.]: Oxford university press, 1941, Call number: PR5907.M25 1941 (Box 59)
  - Gladstone, a biography. New York: E.P. Dutton, 1964, Call number: DA563.4.M3 1964 (Box 27)
  - New life. New York: Farrar, Straus and Cudahy, 1961, Call number: PS3563.A4 N4 1961 (Box 41)
  - Mallarme introduced and edited by Anthony Hartley; with plain prose translations. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1965, Call number: PQ2344.A17 1965 (Box 54)
  - Stephane Mallarme: selected poems translated by C.F. MacIntyre. Berkeley, Calif: University of California Press, 1957, Call number: PQ2344.S74 1957 (Box 56)
  - Royal way translated by Stuart Gilbert. New York: Random House, 1955, Call number: PQ2625.A716 V62 (Box 42)
  - Travels of Sir John Mandeville: with three narratives in illustration of it: The voyage of Johannes de Plano Carpini, The journal of Friar William de Rubruquis, The journal of Friar Odoric. New York: Dover Publications, 1964, Call number: G370.M31 1964 (Box 6)
  - Death in Venice: and seven other stories translated from the German by H.T. Lowe-Porter. New York: Vintage Books, 1936, Call number: PT2625.A44T63 1936 (Box 20)
  - Confessions of Felix Krull, confidence man translated from the German by Denver Lindley, with afterword by George Steiner. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PT2625.A44 B313x 1963 (Box 28)
  - Transposed heads: a legend of India translated from the German by H.T. Lowe-Porter. New York: Vintage Books, 1941, Call number: PT2625.A44 V413 1941 (Box 50)
  - Eros kalos: essay on erotic elements in Greek art. Geneva; New York: Nagel Publishers, 1962, Call number: N8217.E6 M3e (Box 2)
  - Eros and civilization: a philosophical inquiry into Freud by Herbert Marcuse; with a new preface by the author. New York: Vintage Books, 1955, Call number: BF173.M3566 1955 (Box 42)
  - Trois reformateurs: Luther--Descartes--Rousseau. Avec six portraits. Paris: Plon-Nourrit et cie, 1925, Call number: B792.M33t (Box 7)
  - French poetry from Baudelaire to the present: with English prose translations introduced and edited by Elaine Marks. [New York: Dell Pub. Co.], 1962, Call number: PQ1184.M27 (Box 1)
  - Never live twice. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PS3563.A67395 N48 1964 (Box 53)
  - Marvell selected, with an introduction and notes by Joseph H. Summers. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1961, Call number: PR3546.A6 1961 (Box 42)
  - Man on a nylon string. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1963, Call number: PS3563.A835 M36 1963 (Box 50)
  - Boule de Suif, and other stories a new translation by Andrew R. MacAndrew, with a foreword by Edward D. Sullivan. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PQ2349.B68 1964 (Box 25)
  - Dictionary of foreign terms: found in English and American writings of yesterday and today. New York: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PE1670.M3 (Box 5)
  - Charmed life. New York: Harcourt, Brace, 1955, Call number: PS3525.A1435 C43 1955 (Box 59)
  - Charmed life. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PS3525.A1435 C44 (Box 7)
  - Groves of Academe. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PS3525.A1435 G77 1963 (Box 7)
  - Humanist in the bathtub. [New York]: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PS3525.A1435 Z56 (Box 7)
  - Company she keeps. New York, N.Y.: Dell Pub. Co., 1942, Call number: PS3525.A1435 C66 1942 (Box 40)
  - Cast a cold eye. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PS3525.A1435 C3 1963 (Box 43)
  - Choice of assassins. Toronto; New York: Bantam, 1964, Call number: PS3525.A236 C46 1964 (Box 43)
  - Pride of place. New York: Bantam Books, 1963, Call number: PS3525.A236 P7 1963 (Box 43)
  - McGuffey's sixth eclectic reader. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PE1117.M266 (Box 20)
  - Rise of the West: a history of the human community maps by Bela Petheo. New York: The New American Library; London: New English Library, 1965, Call number: CB59.M3 1965 (Box 40)
  - Shorter novels of Herman Melville with an introduction by Raymond Weaver. [New York]: Liveright Pub. Co., 1942, Call number: PS2382.W4 1942 (Box 52)
  - Bramble bush. New York: Bantam, 1958, Call number: PS3525.E6 B737 1958 (Box 43)
  - Maurice Utrillo. Paris: Editions Braun, 1900, Call number: ND553.U87 M4 1900z (Box 37)
  - Golem: a novel [Translated by Madge Pemberton]. New York: F. Ungar, 1964, Call number: PT2625.E95 G65 1964 (Box 13)
  - Really the blues. New York: Random House, 1946, Call number: ML419.M57 A2 (Box 6)
  - Really the blues with a preface by Henry Miller. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: ML419.M5 A3 1964 (Box 40)
  - Miserable miracle: mescaline; with eight drawings by the author [translated by Louise Varese]. San Francisco: City Lights Books, 1963, Call number: QP921.M4 M523 (Box 37)
  - Satanism and witchcraft: a study in medieval superstition translated by A.R. Allinson. New York: Citadel Press, 1960, Call number: BF1569.M62 1960 (Box 26)
  - Listening walls. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3525.I4862 L57 1964 (Box 43)
  - Renascence: and other poems. New York: M. Kennerley, 1917, Call number: PS3525.I495 R4 1917 (Box 58)
  - Rosy crucifixion. New York: Grove Press, 1965, Call number: PS3525.M615ro 1965 v.1 (Box 27)
  - Rosy crucifixion. New York: Grove Press, 1965, Call number: PS3525.M615ro 1965 v.2 (Box 56)
  - Kitten with a whip. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1959, Call number: PS3573.A3 K57 (Box 18)
  - Milton: poems and selected prose edited and with an introduction by Marjorie Hope Nicolson. New York: Bantam, 1962, Call number: PR3552.N53 1962 (Box 8)
  - Student's Milton: being the complete poems of John Milton with the greater part of his prose works, now printed in one volume, together with new translations into English of his Italian, Latin, and Greek poems edited by Frank Allen Patterson. New York: Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1961, Call number: PR3551.P3 1961 (Box 52)
  - Paradise lost; edited by Merritt Y. Hughes. New York: Odyssey Press, 1935, Call number: PR3560.A1 1935 (Box 58)
  - History of Russian literature: from its beginnings to 1900. New York: Vintage Books, 1958, Call number: PG2951.M49 1958 (Box 41)
  - Anchor anthology of short fiction of the seventeenth century selected and edited by Charles C. Mish. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1963, Call number: PR1295.A5 1963 (Box 55)
  - Other side of the hill. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden, 1963, Call number: PS3525.O219 O74 1963 (Box 19)
  - One act: short plays of the modern theatre. New York: Grove Press, 1961, Call number: PN6112.M54 1961 (Box 36)
  - Conjugal love translated from the Italian by Angus Davidson. New York: Farrar, Straus and Young, 1951, Call number: PQ4835.P652 A5E (Box 5)
  - Empty canvas translated by Angus Davidson. New York: New American Library, 1962, Call number: PQ4829.O62 N6413 1962 (Box 18)
  - Christopher Columbus, mariner maps by Erwin Raisz. [New York]: New American Library, 1956, Call number: E111.M863 1955 (Box 27)
  - Sexual behavior of the American college girl. New York: Lancer, 1963, Call number: HQ18.U5 M67 1963 (Box 8)
  - Rothschilds: a family portrait. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1963, Call number: HG1552.R8 M6 1963 (Box 43)
  - Mozart's letters edited and introduced by Eric Blom; selected from the letters of Mozart and his family, translated and annotated by Emily Anderson. Harmondsworth, Middlesex, England; Baltimore, Md.: Penguin, 1956, Call number: ML410.M9 A1954 1956 (Box 40)
  - Introduction to Russian literature. New York: Dutton, 1964, Call number: PG2951.M8 1964 (Box 28)
  - Unicorn. [New York]: Avon, 1965, Call number: PR6063.U7 U54 1965 (Box 45)
  - God of the witches. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1960, Call number: BF1566.M8 1960 (Box 45)
  - Art of the renaissance. New York: Praeger, 1963, Call number: N6370.M96a 1963 (Box 66)
  - Hotel room. New York, N.Y.: Dell, 1964, Call number: PT8950.M9 T9813 1964 (Box 26)
  - Pale fire a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. New York: Lancer Books, 1963, Call number: PS3527.A15 P3 1963 (Box 8)
  - Gift translated from the Russian by Michael Scammell with the collaboration of the author. New York: Popular Library, 1963, Call number: PG3476.N3 D313 1963 (Box 44)
  - Nabokov's dozen. New York, [N.Y.]: Popular Library, 1960, Call number: PS3527.A15 A6287 1960 (Box 46)
  - Unfortunate traveller: or, The life of Jack Wilton newly edited, with an introduction by John Berryman; with 6 original illustrations by Michael Ayrton. New York: Putnam, 1960, Call number: PR2724.U56 1960 (Box 13)
  - National poetry festival held in the Library of Congress October 22-24, 1962: proceedings General Reference and Bibliography Division, Reference Department, Library of Congress. Washington D.C.: General Reference and Bibliography Division, Reference Department, Library of Congress, 1964, Call number: PS305.N38 1964 (Box 26)
  - Origins and history of consciousness with a foreword by C.G. Jung; translated from the German by R.F.C. Hull. New York: Harper, 1962, Call number: BF311.N488 1962 (Box 46, 26)
    Vol.1 in box 46, vol.2 in box 26.
  - Amor and Psyche: the psychic development of the feminine: a commentary on the tale by Apuleius translated from the German by Ralph Manheim. New York: Harper & Row, 1962, Call number: PA6209.M5 N4 1962 (Box 46)
  - Pocket history of the United States. New York: Washington Square Press, inc., 1965, Call number: E178.N41s 1956b (Box 7)
  - Essential Newman edited by Vincent Ferrer Blehl. [New York]: New American Library, 1963, Call number: BX890.N417 (Box 19)
  - John Milton: a reader's guide to his poetry. New York: Noonday Press, 1963, Call number: PR3588.N5 1963 (Box 45)
  - Thus spake Zarathustra translated by Thomas Common. New York: Carlton House, 1935, Call number: B3313.A46E 1935 (Box 58)
  - My life in court. New York: Pyramid Books, 1963, Call number: KF220.N5 1963 (Box 43)
  - Does it make into a bed? New York: Popular Library, 1964, Call number: PS3564.O898 D64 1964 (Box 43)
  - Last hurrah. New York: Bantam Books, 1957, Call number: PS3529.O183l 1957 (Box 27)
  - Edge of sadness. New York: Bantam Books, 1962, Call number: PS3565.C55 E34125 1962 (Box 43)
  - Ten North Frederick. New York: Bantam Books, 1963, Call number: PS3529.O36t 1963 (Box 27)
  - Lockwood concern, a novel. New York: Random House, 1965, Call number: PS3529.O36l (Box 28)
  - Hellbox. New York: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PS3529.H29 H4 1961 (Box 43)
  - Sermons and soda-water. New York: Bantam Books, 1962, Call number: PS3529.H29 S47 1962 (Box 43)
  - Ourselves to know. Toronto; New York: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PS3529.H29 O9 1961 (Box 46)
  - 49 stories. New York: Modern Library, 1962, Call number: PS3529.H29 F68 1962 (Box 52)
  - Royte pomerantsen: Jewish folk humor gathered and edited by Immanuel Olsvanger. New York: Schocken Books, 1965, Call number: PJ5128.O52 1965 (Box 44)
  - Kennedy government. New York: Popular Library, 1961, Call number: E841.O65 1961 (Box 46)
  - Contemporary poet as artist and critic: eight symposia. Boston: Little, Brown, 1964, Call number: PS324.O83 1964 (Box 46)
  - Naked society. New York: Pocket Books, inc., 1964, Call number: JC599.U5 P36 1964 (Box 19)
  - Golden treasury of the best songs and lyrical poems. [New York]: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR1175.P17g 1961 (Box 27)
  - Green ace. New York, N.Y.: Pyramid Books, 1964, Call number: PS3531.A3868 G7 1964 (Box 19)
  - English prose and verse from Beowulf to Stevenson. New York: H. Holt and company, 1915, Call number: PR1109.P3 (Box 68)
  - Trial of Callista Blake. New York: Dell, 1963, Call number: PS3566.A56 T7 1963 (Box 43)
  - Studies in iconology: humanistic themes in the art of the Renaissance. New York: Harper & Row, 1962, Call number: N6370.P3 1962 (Box 45)
  - Oregon Trail with an introduction by A.B. Guthrie, Jr. New York: New American Library, 1950, Call number: F592.P284 1950 (Box 46)
  - Pensees et opuscules: avec une notice biographique, une notice historique et litteraire, des notes explicatives, des jugements, un questionnaire et des sujets de devoirs par J.-Roger Charbonnel. Paris: Larousse, 1934, Call number: B1901.P4 1934 (Box 48)
  - In the interlude: poems, 1945-1960 translated into English verse by Henry Kamen; with a foreward by Sir Maurice Bowra and notes by George Katkov. London; New York: Oxford University Press, 1962, Call number: PG3476.P27 A237 1962 (Box 49)
  - Renaissance with an introduction by Kenneth Clark. Cleveland: World Publishing Company, 1961, Call number: N6915.P3 1961 (Box 47)
  - Sunset touch. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden-Bartell, 1964, Call number: PS3566.E215 S86 1964 (Box 43)
  - Story of language. New York: New American Library, 1960, Call number: P121.P45 1960 (Box 46)
  - Moviegoer. New York: Popular Library, 1961, Call number: PS3566.E6912 M6 1961b (Box 43)
  - Death mask. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1959, Call number: PR6031.A49 D43 1959 (Box 43)
  - Spectral boy: poems. Middletown, Conn.: Wesleyan University Press, 1964, Call number: PS3566.E83 S6 1964 (Box 50)
  - Counterfeit lady unveiled and other criminal fiction of seventeenth-century England: a selection with forewords and notes. New York: Doubleday, 1961, Call number: PR1309.D4 P48 1961 (Box 46)
  - Aesthetics today: readings selected, edited, and introduced. Cleveland: World Pub. Co., 1961, Call number: N79.P45 1961 (Box 48)
  - Avon book of modern writing: a collection of original contributions by today's leading writers: Robert Musil ... [et al.]. New York: Avon Publ., 1953, Call number: PN6014.P48 v.2 (Box 49)
  - Desire: a play translated from the French by Bernard Frechtman. New York: Philosphical Library, 1948, Call number: PQ2631.I37 D42 1948 (Box 58)
  - Hanno's doll. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcette Publications, 1964, Call number: PS3531.I76 H36 1964x (Box 19)
  - Dialogues of Plato Jowett translation; edited and with introductory notes by J.D. Kaplan. New York: Washington Square Press, 1951, Call number: B358.J854 1951 (Box 8)
  - Plato, the Republic translated with an introduction by H.D.P. Lee. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1955, Call number: JC71.P35 1955b (Box 18)
  - Lives of the noble Grecians and Romans translated by John Dryden and revised by Arthur Hugh Clough. New York: The Modern library, 1932, Call number: DE7.P5 1932 (Box 41)
  - Fall of the Roman Republic: Marius, Sulla, Crassus, Pompey, Caesar Cicero: six lives translated by Rex Warner. Harmondsworth, Middlesex: Penguin Books, 1958, Call number: DG254.2.P553 1958 (Box 48)
  - Rise and fall of Athens: nine Greek lives: Theseus, Solon, Themistocles, Aristides, Cimon, Pericles, Nicias, Alcibiades, Lysander by Plutarch; translated with an introduction by Ian Scott-Kilvert. [Harmondsworth, Middlesex]: Penguin Books; Baltimore, Md., 1960, Call number: PA4374.V81 S3 1960 (Box 48)
    SEE: Rago, Henry.
  - Klee: biographical and critical study translated from the Italian by James Emmons. [Lausanne]: Skira; [distributed by World Pub. Co., Cleveland, 1960, Call number: ND588.K6 P77E (Box 30)
  - Alexander Pope: selected poetry & prose edited with an introduction by William K. Wimsatt, Jr. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1951, Call number: PR3622.W5 1951 (Box 50)
  - Our language. Baltimore, Penguin Books, 1963, Call number: PE1095.P85o (Box 25)
  - Evil wish. New York: Ace Books, 1962, Call number: PS3531.O789 E94 (Box 19)
  - Ezra Pound: translations with an introduction by Hugh Kenner. [New York]: New Directions, 1963, Call number: PN6020.P6 1963 (Box 50)
  - I take this land. New York: Bantam, 1964, Call number: PS3531.O966 I2 1964 (Box 43)
  - Battles that changed history. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1956, Call number: D25.P68 1956 (Box 43)
  - History of the conquest of Mexico with an introduction by Henry Bamford Parkes. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: F1230.P9692 1964 (Box 46)
  - History of the conquest of Peru: the classic story of the Inca Empire and its subjugation by the Spaniards with an introduction, new notes, and a new summary of the civil wars and subsequent events by Victor W. von Hagen. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: F3442.P9332 1961 (Box 46)
  - Three modern French plays of the imagination. [New York: Dell Pub. Co.], 1966, Call number: PC2117.P68 (Box 30)
  - Remembrance of things past translated by C. K. Scott-Moncrieff; introduction by Joseph Wood Krutch. New York: Random house, 1934, Call number: PQ2631.P94 A1E 1934 v.1 (Box 6)
  - Remembrance of things past translated by C. K. Scott-Moncrieff. New York: Random House, 1932, Call number: PQ2631.P94 A1E 1932 v.2 (Box 6)
  - Within a budding grove translated by C.K. Scott Moncrieff. New York: Modern Library, 1951, Call number: PQ2631.R63 W58 1951 (Box 6)
  - Swann's way translated from the French, by C.K. Scott Moncrieff. New York: A. & C. Boni, 1930, Call number: PQ2631.R63 D813 1930 (Box 28)
  - Amour de Swann. Paris: Gallimard, 1964, Call number: PQ2631.R63 A47 1964 (Box 48)
  - Marcel Proust on art and literature, 1896-1919 translated by Sylvia Townsend Warner. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1964, Call number: PQ2631.R63 C713 1964 (Box 49)
  - Byron in Italy. New York: Viking Press, 1957, Call number: PR4382.Q42 1957 (Box 52)
  - Journey into terror: an original Gold Medal book. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1957, Call number: PS3568.A233 J68 1957 (Box 43)
  - Histories of Gargantua and Pantagruel translated and with an introduction by J. M. Cohen. Harmondsworth, Middlesex; New York: Penguin Books, 1955, Call number: PQ1685.E5 C6 (Box 41)
  - Fraud: a novel. New York: Bantam Books, 1962, Call number: PS3568.A3 F72 1962 (Box 20)
  - Literature in America: an anthology of literary criticism selected and introduced by Philip Rahv. New York: Meridian Books, 1957, Call number: PS121.R2 1957 (Box 49)
  - Concise history of modern painting. New York: Praeger, 1964, Call number: ND195.R4 1964 (Box 49)
  - English prose style Herbert Read. Boston: Beacon Press, 1952, Call number: PE1421.R35 1952 (Box 49)
  - Meaning of art. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1949, Call number: N7425.R4 1949 (Box 53)
  - Capricorn rhyming dictionary: (aid to rhyme). New York: Capricorn Books, 1965, Call number: PE1519.R4 1965 (Box 67)
  - King must die. New York: Pocket Books, 1960, Call number: PR6035.E55 K5 1960 (Box 42)
  - Kingside. New York: Paperback Library, 1964, Call number: PS3568.E619 K56 1964 (Box 44)
  - Russian through pictures. New York: Washington Square Press-, 1961, Call number: PG2121.R5 1961 (Box 54)
  - Coleridge on imagination. Bloomington: Indiana University Press, 1960, Call number: PR4487.I6 R5 1960 (Box 49)
  - Duino elegies the German text, with an English translation, introduction, and commentary by J. B. Leishman and Stephen Spender. New York: W.W. Norton & Company, Inc., 1939, Call number: PT2635.R45 D8E 1939 (Box 70)
    Copy 1 in box 70, copy 2 in box 9.
  - Notebooks of Malte Laurids Brigge translated by M. D. Herter Norton. New York: Norton, 1964, Call number: PT2635.I65 N6 1964 (Box 5)
  - New poems: The German text with a translation, introduction, and notes by J. B. Leishman. [New York]: New Directions, 1964, Call number: PT2635.R45 A17E 1964a (Box 9)
  - Sonnets to Orpheus translated by M. D. Herter Norton. New York: W. W. Norton & company, inc., 1942, Call number: PT2635.R45 S6 1942 (Box 9)
  - Translations from the poetry of Rainer Maria Rilke translated by M.D. Herter Norton. New York: Norton, 1962, Call number: PT2635.I65 A255 1962 (Box 14)
  - Ausgewahlten Gedichte. Erster Teil [ausgewahlt von Katharina Kippenberg]. Wiesbaden: Insel Verlag, 1959, Call number: PT2635.I65 A6 1959 (Box 20)
  - Selected works. London: Hogarth Press, 1954, Call number: PT2635.R45 A14E 1954 v.2 (Box 22)
  - Letters to a young poet translation by M.D. Herter Norton. New York: Norton, 1963, Call number: PT2635.I65 Z54 1963 (Box 49)
  - Stories of God translation by M.D. Herter Norton. New York: Norton, 1963, Call number: PT2635.I65 V62 1963 (Box 50)
  - Selected letters of Rainer Maria Rilke edited by Harry T. Moore. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1960, Call number: PT2635.I65 Z4813 1960 (Box 54)
  - Rimbaud; [selected verse] with plain prose translations of each poem introduced and edited by Oliver Bernard. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1962, Call number: PQ2387.R5 A17E 1962 (Box 27)
  - Circular staircase. New York, N.Y.: Dell, 1963, Call number: PS3535.I73 C47 1963 (Box 19)
  - After house. New York: Dell, 1965, Call number: PS3535.I73 A8 1965 (Box 32)
  - Great mistake. New York City: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3535.I73 G7 1964 (Box 67)
  - Miss Pinkerton. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3535.I73 M5 1964 (Box 67)
  - Two novels translated by Richard Howard. New York: Grove Press, 1965, Call number: PQ2635.R532 J3E 1965 (Box 46)
  - Voyeur translated by Richard Howard. New York: Grove Press, 1958, Call number: PQ2635.R532 V9E (Box 49)
  - Honest to God. Philadelphia: Westminster Press, 1963, Call number: BT55.R55h (Box 19)
  - Far field. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1964, Call number: PS3535.R628f (Box 28)
  - American procession: American life since 1860 in photographs assembled by Agnes Rogers; with running comment by Frederick Lewis Allen. New York, London: Harper & brothers, 1933, Call number: E161.R74 1933 (Box 35)
  - Face to face. New York: Macfadden-Bartell Book, 1963, Call number: PS3568.O434 F3 1963 (Box 56)
  - Corner on angels. New York: Dell, 1963, Call number: PS3568.O4353 C67 1963 (Box 53)
  - Scandal in Eden. New York: Dell Pub., 1964, Call number: PS3535.O414 S33 1964 (Box 56)
  - Death of a nobody translated by Desmond MacCarthy and Sidney Waterlow; with a new introduction by the author, translated by Haakon Chevalier; afterword by Maurice Natanson. [New York] New American Library, 1961, Call number: PQ2635.O52 M673 1961 (Box 12)
  - Knock, ou, Le triomphe de la medecine edited with introduction, notes and vocabulary by Albert Douglas Menut and Dwight Ingersoll Chapman. New York: Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1937, Call number: PQ2635.O52 K6 1937 (Box 58)
  - Murder in the family. New York: Belmont, 1964, Call number: PR6035.O666 M87 1964 (Box 48)
  - Amours Ronsard; [texte etabli, presente et annote par Albert-Marie Schmidt.]. [Paris]: Gallimard et Librairie Generale Francaise, 1964, Call number: PQ1676 .A6 1964 (Box 9)
  - Tradition of the new. New York: Grove Press, 1961, Call number: PS3535.O698 T69 1961 (Box 49)
  - Vertical & horizontal. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1963, Call number: PS3568.O8353 V47 1963 (Box 48)
  - Channing. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PS3568.O8439 C43 1964 (Box 57)
  - Coast to coast. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden-Bartell, 1963, Call number: PN1.M26 1963 (Box 57)
  - Greece translated from the Russian by J.D. Duff. New York: Oxford University Press, 1963, Call number: DF214.R713 1963 (Box 49)
  - Renoir: biographical and critical studies translated by James Emmons. [Geneva]: Skira, 1954, Call number: ND553.R45 R65 1954 (Box 51)
  - Alcohol: its history, folklore, and its effect on the human body. New York: Grove Press, 1962, Call number: HV5060.R9 1962 (Box 54)